xpenology.nl 2015-04-08

# Privacy Statement - XPEnology.nl

## **Privacy Statement**

We respect the privacy of visitors to the website and shall ensure that the personal information you give us is confidential. Processing of personal data is done in a manner that is consistent with the requirements of the Data Protection Act.

## Purposes of the data

Your personal data will be processed by us for management information, product and service development, determining our strategy by conducting analyzes and fulfilling legal obligations.

## Click behavior and visitor information

General visitor data is kept on the website. In this context, particularly the IP address of your computer, any user name, time of extraction and data that the browser sends a visitor is recorded and used for statistical analysis of visits and clicks on the website. It also allows us to optimize the operation of the website.

We try these data as anonymous as possible. This information will not be provided to third parties.

## Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track how users use the site and have enabled the Google Analytics ad functions for obtaining demographic and interest reports. The resulting information, including the address of your computer (IP address), transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Please read the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.nl/intl/nl/policies/privacy/) for more information, as well as specific to Google Analytics. You can exclude yourself from our web statistics by using this [Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

Google uses this information to track how our website is used, to provide reports on the website to us and to provide its advertisers information about the effectiveness of their campaigns. Google may also transfer this information to third parties if Google is legally required, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. We have no influence. We have Google only permitted to use the information obtained analytics service from Google itself.

## Use of cookies

Through our website, cookies are placed from the US company Google, as part of the “Analytics” service. We use this service to track and get reports about how visitors use the site. Google may also transfer this information to third parties if Google is legally required, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. We have no influence.

## Remarketing

Also, we place a cookie on the use of a re-marketing service. This allows us to ads on other websites (including Google) to show previous visitors of our website. For example, previous visitors who have not completed a task on our website, such as filling out a contact form. These ads on the search results pages of Google, or displayed on a site with banners. Opt Out: You can opt out of the use of this cookie using the settings that you can find on the ‘i’ shown in the ad.

## Adjusting privacy statement

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement. Changes will be published on this website.
